Michał Kareńko

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

mkarenko.com

+48 692 566 688



I have over three years of commercial experience as a front-end developer. During this time I have refined my skills working with React, utilizing technologies such as Ionic, CSS, and REST API. When creating websites and applications I pay great attention to detail to ensure that the final product meets the client's expectations and it is of the highest quality. I am remarkable at paying attention to details and have a precise approach to executing each task.

TECHNOLOGIES

- React.js
- JavaScript
- Typescript
- HTML, CSS, Tailwind
- Flutter
- Dart
- REST API
- Recoil
- Redux
- Ionic
- Git
- GitHub, Bitbucket
- Firebase, Supabase
- Linux, Windows

LANGUAGES

- Polish (Native)
- English (C1)

EDUCATION

2014 - 2017 University of Łódź Faculty of Physics and Applied Informatics

EXPERIENCE

Billog Studio 2021 - currently Junior Front-end Developer

- Participating in team projects, developing and improving products and services, implementing new technologies and tools.
- Designing, implementing, testing software and introducing improvements.
- Managing projects from a technical perspective, maintaing existing code and resolving issues related to the application's functionality.

Rekeep Poland 2020 - 2021 Junior IT Specialist

- Monitoring computer networks and troubleshooting hardware and software issues.
- Technical support for users, including remote work, system updates and configuration in compliance with security policies.

GG24 AB 2019 - 2020 IT Technician

- Managed computer networks, designed network models, and resolved software and hardware issues.
- Provided end-user support and conducted basic training.
- Maintained and replaced computer equipment as needed.